NIKITA ABLAMSKIY

Frontend engineer



ablamskiy.n@gmail.com

Education

Technical College of Management, Informatization and Service

2021 - 2024 Russia, Krasnodar

Skills

Linux

HTML	•	•	•	\	\Diamond

CSS	•		\Diamond

JavaScript/TypeScript	•	•	\	•	\Diamond
React/Next	•	4	4	^	\Diamond

Svelte	•	\	•	\Q	\Diamond

LITIUX					\
Docker	♦			\Diamond	\Diamond

Tailwind CSS	•	•	•	•	\Diamond
	•	•	•	•	~

SASS	•	\	\	•	

Networking	•	\Diamond	\Diamond

Links

1 fly0utwest

flyOutwest
https://flyOutwest.dev

Professional summary

I'm a web developer with a burning passion for crafting scalable and user-friendly web apps that captivate users at first click. I'm always on the hunt, exploring new tech and frameworks to innovate and solve challenges. I have experience writing SPA with *Sveltekit*, *React/Next* and its server components, *SCSS*, Tailwind and *TypeScript*, using *Feature Sliced Design* as frontend methodology. I also have written some backend in **Java/Spring**. In addition to this I've worked with **Linux**, **Docker**, built some *CI/CD pipelines*. Now I look for new possibilities for learning and enhancing my abilities as a developer.

Experience

April 2024 - Now https://aielts.ru aiELTS - educational platform for IELTS exam preparation

Developed landing and other interface elements and widgets like profile with SvelteKit for the platform, also worked with PocketBase and helped with design system and UI/UX

Pet-projects

January 2024 - April 2024

Bookmarked

My graduation project - fullstack letterboxd-like cinematic platform for tracking watched media history. Wrote in Spring, React/TS, SASS

August 2024 -

f0wdotdev

My potrfolio web app written in NextJS and Tailwind

Languages

♦ English ♦ Russian ♦ Ukrainian

Hobbies

- Basic networking
- System administration

Personal info

♦ Date of birth: 30 September 2003